<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Weekly Chan Times</title>
    <link>https://weekly-chan-times.firebaseapp.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Weekly Chan Times</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://weekly-chan-times.firebaseapp.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The ChanTimes - Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://weekly-chan-times.firebaseapp.com/posts/vol_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weekly-chan-times.firebaseapp.com/posts/vol_2/</guid>
      <description>In Search of Negative Space Vol. 2: July 1 - July 8 I&amp;rsquo;m a workaholic and only feel satisfied when I&amp;rsquo;m creating &amp;hellip; There&amp;rsquo;s no way I can keep working at this unsustainable pace.
My mind has been vacillating over these thoughts for the last week. I wake up each morning at 6:40 am, slide out of bed and shower by 7, head downstairs to pack camera gear for the day at 7:30, set up AV equipment for check-in at 8:30, and then work non-stop through the day until I can escape work by 9:00 at night (at the earliest).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ChanTimes - Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://weekly-chan-times.firebaseapp.com/posts/vol_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weekly-chan-times.firebaseapp.com/posts/vol_4/</guid>
      <description>Tilt Your Head Back and Laugh at the Sky Vol. 4 - July 16th to 23rd : 2018 I&amp;rsquo;m afraid that I will run out of words. That I&amp;rsquo;ll get deeper into my meditation practice and realize that I have nothing left to say. My life will be defined by how I live it, and not how I archive and talk about it.
And yet, I am compelled to catalogue my existence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ChanTimes - Vol. 3</title>
      <link>https://weekly-chan-times.firebaseapp.com/posts/vol_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weekly-chan-times.firebaseapp.com/posts/vol_3/</guid>
      <description>Stopping to Smell the Roses Lavender Vol. 3 - July 9th to 15th : 2018 &amp;ldquo;The brain I think is pretty much insane &amp;hellip; I think this thing is a scanning device built for survival looking for things that are wrong so that you can avoid them. I now know that I am not the voices in my mind &amp;hellip; when you sit and practice meditation you start to identify more with the space between the thoughts than the thoughts themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ChanTimes - Vol. 1</title>
      <link>https://weekly-chan-times.firebaseapp.com/posts/vol_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://weekly-chan-times.firebaseapp.com/posts/vol_1/</guid>
      <description>Car Wrecks and Mood Swings Vol. 1 - June 24 - June 31 : 2018 Sometimes life kicks you in the face and all you can do is get back up bucktoothed and smiling.
Today was one of those days. After working from 8am to 6pm with nothing to show for it, I was ready to get out of Wayne State and back home to Facetime Madeline. My talk with her was supposed to be my day&amp;rsquo;s salvation - when all of the stress and troubles of the day would be atoned and I would have a burst of levity, laughter outside of the pressure of the VFA bubble.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>